Pillowtalk - Zayn Malik
[00:15.60]
Climb on board
We'll go slow and high tempo
安全登陆
Light and dark
我们可以慢慢感受也可以快速冲击
Hold me hard and mellow
引爆黑夜
I'm seeing the pain seeing the pleasure
紧拥我 感受你的芳醇
Nobody but you 'body but me 'body but us
痛苦 快乐 我都经历过
Bodies together
除了你和我 除了我们之外没人
I'd love to hold you close tonight and always
能像我们这样水乳交融
I'd love to wake up next to you
今夜我想紧拥你 永远这样
I'd love to hold you close tonight and always
我想在你身旁醒来
I'd love to wake up next to you
今夜我想紧拥你 永远这样
So we'll piss off the neighbors
我想在你身旁醒来
In the place that feels the tears
我们会惹毛所有的邻居
The place to lose your fears
在这个你能感受泪水的地方
Yeah reckless behavior
在这个你不再恐惧害怕的地方
A place that is so pure so dirty and raw
你的不顾一切
Be in the bed all day bed all day bed all day
这个地方是那么纯粹又是那么肮脏阴冷
Fucking you and fighting on
所有剧情都在床榻间上演 都在床榻间上演
It's our paradise and it's our war zone
激情缠绵 争执不休
这里既是我们的天堂又是我们的战场
Pillow talk
My enemy my ally
枕边絮语
Prisoners
我的敌人 我的战友
Then we're free it's a thriller
我们都是囚徒
I'm seeing the pain seeing the pleasure
而后我们重获自由 这令人颤栗
Nobody but you 'body but me 'body but us
痛苦 快乐 我都经历过
Bodies together
除了你和我 除了我们之外
I'd love to hold you close tonight and always
能像我们这样水乳交融
I'd love to wake up next to you
今夜我想紧拥你 永远这样
So we'll piss off the neighbors
我想在你身旁醒来
In the place that feels the tears
我们会惹毛所有的邻居
The place to lose your fears
在这个你能感受泪水的地方
Yeah reckless behavior
在这个你不再恐惧害怕的地方
A place that is so pure so dirty and raw
你的不顾一切
Be in the bed all day bed all day bed all day
这个地方是那么纯粹又是那么肮脏阴冷
Fucking you and fighting on
所有剧情都在床榻间上演 都在床榻间上演
It's our paradise and it's our war zone
激情缠绵 争执不休
这里既是我们的天堂又是我们的战场
Paradise paradise paradise paradise
War zone war zone war zone war zone
天堂乐园 天堂乐园
Paradise paradise paradise paradise
我们的战场
War zone war zone war zone war zone
天堂乐园 天堂乐园
So we'll piss off the neighbors
我们的战场
In the place that feels the tears
我们会惹毛所有的邻居
The place to lose your fears
在这个你能感受泪水的地方
Yeah reckless behavior
在这个你不再恐惧害怕的地方
A place that is so pure so dirty and raw
你的不顾一切
Be in the bed all day bed all day bed all day
这个地方是那么纯粹又是那么肮脏阴冷
Fucking you and fighting on
所有剧情都在床榻间上演 都在床榻间上演
It's our paradise and it's our war zone
激情缠绵 争执不休
这里既是我们的天堂又是我们的战场
[03:20.68]
[ml:1.0]